https://philhellmuth.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The PHILHELLMUTH.COM (“PHILHELLMUTH.COM”) privacy policy is below.
Privacy Statement for PHILHELLMUTH.COM
PHILHELLMUTH.COM has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for PHILHELLMUTH.COM and all Web sites powered by PHILHELLMUTH.COM.
Use of your IP address
PHILHELLMUTH.COM uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.
Use of cookies
PHILHELLMUTH.COM uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to keep track of your membership status on the Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. The cookies we use only track your currently logged in status or your shopping cart status.
Use of registration form information
PHILHELLMUTH.COM’s registration form requires users to give us Registration Contact Information (“Registration Contact Information” includes but is not limited to user name and e-mail address) and Demographic Information (“Demographic Information” includes but is not limited to user zip code). We use Registration Contact Information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and other companies. The Registration Contact Information also is used to contact the user when necessary and may be shared with other select companies. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings (see the choice/opt-out section below). User Demographic Information and user profile data also is collected at our Web site. We use this Demographic Information and user profile data to customize the user’s experience at our Web site, showing the user content that PHILHELLMUTH.COM thinks the user might be interested in, and displaying the content according to the user’s preferences. We do not share mailing address, credit card, or any personally identifiable information (other than e-mail address and date of birth) with other companies; except where we have the customer’s prior consent to share such information. Demographic Information and profile data are used only for personalized Web content and statistical information and are not shared with other companies except in ways that do not personally identify users of our Web site.
Links to other Web sites
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Philhellmuth.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We may place advertising on our Web site that originates from third party advertisers and/or advertising agencies. Even though these advertisements are embedded in our Web site cookies may be assigned by the advertisers and not PHILHELLMUTH.COM. PHILHELLMUTH.COM does not control those cookies.
Use of order form information
Our Web site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect user’s Order Contact Information (“Order Contact Information” includes but is not limited to user name and e-mail address) and financial information (“Financial Information” includes but is not limited to credit card numbers). Order Contact Information from the order form is used to send to the user the user’s order and information about our company and other companies. The Order Contact Information also is used to communicate with the user when necessary and may be shared with other select companies. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings (see the choice/opt-out section below). Financial Information and Order Contact Information also is used to bill the user for products and services purchased by the user and may be shared with companies that help PHILHELLMUTH.COM operate our Web site, such as credit card companies.
Use of contest form information
PHILHELLMUTH.COM executes and administers contests on our Web site in which PHILHELLMUTH.COM asks users for Contest Contact Information (“Contest Contact Information” includes but is not limited to user name and e-mail address) and Demographic Information. PHILHELLMUTH.COM uses Contest Contact Information to send users information about our company and other companies. The Contest Contact Information also is used to contact the user when necessary and may be shared with other select companies. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings (see the choice/opt-out section below). User Demographic Information and profile data also is collected at our Web site. PHILHELLMUTH.COM uses this Demographic Information and profile data to customize our user’s experience at our Web site, showing the user content that PHILHELLMUTH.COM thinks the user might be interested in, and displaying the content according to the user’s preferences. PHILHELLMUTH.COM may share Contest Contact Information and Demographic Information with the contest prize providers.
Use of aggregated information
PHILHELLMUTH.COM collects and stores statistics and other information about the online activities of our users on an aggregated (collected) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts.
PHILHELLMUTH.COM may assign, sell, license or otherwise transfer to a third party any information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of all or substantially all of the assets or capital stock of PHILHELLMUTH.COM or its affiliated entities.
PHILHELLMUTH.COM may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.
Public Forums
This Web site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. PHILHELLMUTH.COM may be required to release personal information about users as a result of a lawsuit or subpoena or as immediately necessary to protect our rights or the rights and safety of others. Additionally, “perfect security” does not exist on the internet.
Children’s Guidelines
PHILHELLMUTH.COM strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children’s online activities and to consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personally identifiable information without parental permission. Tickets and products for sale are intended for purchase by adults. By making a purchase on the site, you agree and represent that you are at least 13 years of age.
Although the PHILHELLMUTH.COM site is not directed to children under the age of 13,
PHILHELLMUTH.COM DOES NOT collect online contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child’s request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.
PHILHELLMUTH.COM DOES NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.
PHILHELLMUTH.COM DOES NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.
PHILHELLMUTH.COM DOES NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.
PHILHELLMUTH.COM DOES NOT entice children under the age of 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our Web site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from PHILHELLMUTH.COM and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This Web site gives users the option of removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send e-mail to unsubscribe@philhellmuth.com.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
info@philhellmuth.com
Leave a Reply
Click here to cancel reply.
You must be logged in to post a comment.
right here.
© Copyright Phil Hellmuth | 15 Time World Series of Poker Champion
